Guide to the Delmer Daves Papers, 1930-1965
Department of Special Collections
- The Battle of Villa Fiorita. Part II. (Box 72)
  - TLC-S. CG to GLB re: sending Panavision equipment., 4/1/64
  - TLC. Catherine O'Brien to Max Bercutt re: publicity., 4/19/64; 2 pgs.
  - Telegram. Warner to DD re: production business., 4/23/64
  - TLC. Progress reports and things completed., 5/1/64; 2 copies, 6 pgs. each.
  - IOC-S. Bill Hill to V. Peck re: confirmation of shooting., 5/20/64
  - IOC-S. Bill Hill to V. Peck re: schedule changes., 5/22/64
  - IOC-S. Bill Hill to V. Peck re: equipment needed., 5/22/64
  - IOC-S. Bill Hill to V. Peck re: Maureen O'Hara's dressing room., 5/22/64
  - TLS-verifax. Peter Rogers to GLB. Enjoyed filming sequence in his theatre., 6/17/64
  - TLS. John W. Daran (Publicity dept., Assoc. British Picture Corp. Ltd.) to DD re: compliments on films., 9/7/64
  - TLC [DD] to Bert & Blattner re: premiere results in London & cuts., 10/19/64; 2 pgs
  - ALS Martin [?] to DD. personal., ND; 5 1/2 × 7. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - ALS. illegible. [Written in Italian], 5/25/64
  - ALS from Ruoly Mayr and [Hiky?] to DD. best wishes., ND
  - ALS to DD re: thanks for L10,000., ND; 6 × 8.
  - ALS Olivia [Hussey] to DD re: thanks for gift., 5/14/64; 6 × 8.
  - ALS Maureen [O'Hara] to DD re: best wishes for film., 10/20/64; 6 × 8.
  - ALS Olivia [Hussey] to DD re: thanks for money., ND; 1 page written on both sides.
  - Marguerete West to DD re: best wishes., ND; 5 1/4 × 7.
  - ALS Carmen [?] to DD re: thanks for crib., ND
  - Signed greetings, illegible [Poliansky?] seems to be Spolionsky, ND
  - Tele. Bob Lennerol to DD - best wishes., 5/5/64
  - Tele. MacEwen and Jack [Warner] to DD - best wishes, 5/13/64
  - Tele. Same as # 79., 5/19/64
  - Tele. Unit Crew and cast to DD - best wishes., ND
  - B. Production Worksheets.
  - Cast in order of appearance with charactorizations. M., 1/7/64; 3 pgs. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - IOC-C Hoyt Bowers to JLW re: list of cast suggestions with PNA., 1/28/64
  - T. list of suggestions with PNA., ND
  - T. acting biographies of European actors. 2 pgs. with PNA., ND
  - Directing and editing biography. of Douglas Robertson [Verifax] with PA - address., ND
  - 16 cables from Warner Bros. re: casting progress., 2/5/64-5/28/64 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 5 letters from WB re: casting of actors, other production problems., 2/5/64-4/21/64 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - 4 letters from actors' agents seeking parts., 3/9/64 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Casting List D., ND; 4 × 5 1/2.
  - Technical correspondence 1 TLS, ALS, lists) to & from DD re: needed equipment & filming technique., 2/5/64-5/25/64; 20 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - List of equipment being used on location in Africa. Photocopy., ND (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten notes, scratch work, sketches, cutting notes. P., ND; 11 pgs. 7 × 9, 8 pgs. 8 × 11 1/2, 3 pgs. 8 × 11, 5 pgs. 8 × 14. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - One temporary membership card 3 1/4 × 4 1/4 in Assoc of Cinematograph TV & Allied Technicians. A., ND
  - Leaflet for [Coombe] Hill Riding School., ND; 8°, M.
  - Note on costume. PN., ND; 7 × 9.
  - Diagrams and sketches., ND; 8 pgs. 8 × 11.
  - [Call sheets], etc., 4/9/64-7/9/64; 59 pgs. 4° & 8 × 14. M. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Progress reports on production completed., 5/4/64-7/15/64; 52 pgs. M. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Production cross-plot from script of 1/7/64, ND; 2 pgs. 26 1/2 × 17 3/4. p. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Production cross plot., 5/4/64; 27 × 23. Photocopy.
  - List of available musicians with pN., ND (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Music notes. S., ND
  - Romantico Amore lyrics., ND; 2 copies, 1 carbon.
  - Music for theme for piano & song by C. [Donida?]., ND; 3 photostats.
  - Rumer Godden's notes on Script., ND; 12 pgs. T 8 × 14 with PN by RG and DD. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Italian accomodations & other pertinent information for cast & crew., ND; 4 pgs. C 8 × 14. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Equipment for Italian location., ND; 7 pgs. mimeo 8 × 14. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - List of crew in British filming unit. and PN., ND; 8 × 14. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Equipment & location shooting requirements., ND; 5 pgs. T 8 × 14. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - List of sets in Italy. T with OPN., ND; 11 pgs. 8 × 14. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Useful locational info. M. signed DD in caps on top., 2/22/64; 3 pgs (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Travel Arrangements for Personnel not travelling on charter M., 5-24-64; Legal (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Italian Movement schedule M., 5-25-64; Legal
  - Travel Arrangements M., 5-25-64; Legal
  - Movement order M., 5-26-64; Legal
  - Details of Transport M., NO; Legal
  - Milan Hotel Accomodations. M., 5-25-64; Legal
  - Milan Movement M., 5-25-64; Legal
  - Call Sheet M., 5-28-64; Legal
  - Movement Order (London) M., 5-28-64; Legal
  - Charter Flight personnel M., 5-29-64; Legal
  - UK Movement Order M., 6-4-64; 2pgs.
    return to next page
  - List of crew in Italian unit., ND; 1 pgs. C with OPN 8 × 14. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Set preparations in Italy., ND; 22 pgs. 4° T. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Warner Bros. travelling unit--cast & crew with list of addresses, etc., ND; 4 pgs. 8 × 14. M. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Directory of internal telephones., ND; 7 pgs. 8 × 14 M. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Unit hotel accomodations with room numbers., ND; 2 pgs. M (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Floor plan of Villa Fiorita. 18 1/2 × 23 1/2. Blueprint copy with copy of DD note on verso., ND (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Set description--studio interiors., ND 1; 18 pgs. T small 4°. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - 10 BW photos of sketches of set interiors., ND; 8" × 10". (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - British locations-exterior set descriptions., ND; 2 copies, T and C. Size X. 11pgs each. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Travel itinerary for DD, London to Italy. C., 4/15/64 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Movement order #1 with general travel preparation information, signed by DD. M., 4/27/64; Legal. (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Movement order for storm sequence. M., ND; Legal.
  - Information for unit on arrival in Milan and Gardone, signed by DD. M., 5/1/64; Legal. (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - TLS Bill Hill to Orazio Tassara re: arrange for baggage movement and people meeting unit at airport. C., 5/26/64; Size X.
  - Car seating arrangements. M., 5/1/64; Legal.
  - Travel arrangements to date. C., 5/20/64; Legal. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    See previous page Many items here were never cataloged
  - Movement order M.Legal 14 pgs., 7/7/64
  - IOC-S Bill Hill to Orazio Tassara re: plane tickets and reservations for people. C., 5/7/64
  - IOC-S Bill Hill to Victor Peck re: travel details. C., 5/7/64
  - Notes on Production plans for children's sequences. T., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - 1 week shooting schedule. M., 5/22/64
  - Check list of miscellaneous shots to be filmed, with FPNAD., ND; Legal.
  - Interior shots remaining Legal, 5-18-64; 2 pgs
  - Shooting schedule. M., 6/15/64; Legal. 4 pgs.
  - Shooting schedule. M., 5/22/64; Legal.
  - Progressive schedule #2 with DD signature., 5/9/64; 3 pgs.
  - Progress schedule no. 2 (addition) M., ND
  - 1st draft schedule with DD signature., 4/29/64; Legal. 4 pgs.
  - Miscellaneous shooting schedule. ph., ND; Legal. 4 pgs.
  - Location schedule to completion with OPNAD., ND; Legal.
  - Italy locations. C., ND; 2 pgs. Legal
  - Verifax of test scenes for Michele and Debby., ND; Legal. 3 pgs. (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Script changes, ND; (2 C. pgs., 3 T. pgs.) Legal. 5 pgs. (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Artists' billing. Verifax, with OPA., 6/29/64; 3 pgs. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Certificate of writing credits. Xerox., 8/13/64
  - TCS C. Greenlaw to G. L. Blattner re: getting filming equipment., 3/16/64 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - IOC-S P. D. Knecht to DD re: enclosing copy of legal dubbing provisions for Maureen O'Hara., 5/11/64; 8vo.
  - Legal clause. Xerox., ND; 8 1/2" × 8 1/2".
  - Estimating script., 1/7/64; 145 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Breakdown of sequences, sets, props etc. M., 4/16/64; 87 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Index and breakdown of sequences. C., 2/6/64; 141 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 3)
- A Covenant with Death (WB), 1965
  - Original story by Stephens Becker, cut and pasted on paper with TN and revisions and FPpNAD by DD., ND; ca. 250 pgs. both sides. (Box 74, Folder 4,5)
  - Exploratory SP by DD revised with notes in addendum. FPpNAD., ND; 125 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Foreword, Dilemma and analysis of book, with OPN., 6/30/65; 16 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Comments, analysis and suggestions for development of SP from novel, with OPN., ND; 8 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 1st draft SP. M., 9/7/65; 154 pgs. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Revised draft, 10/8/65; (2 copies). M. 150 pgs. each. (Box 75, Folder 1,2)
  - Cast selection list., 9/20/65; 4 pgs., 2 T and 2 M. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Cast list and description of roles., ND; 2 pgs.
  - Mock up guide., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Blocking, rough guide with FPNAD., ND; 2 pgs (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Dialogue revisions., ND; 2 pgs.
  - Key sequences-hand notes., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Script changes and development., ND; 17 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Production cross-plot (actors and scenes) P., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Tearsheet- A Covenant with Death Pt II by Stephen Becker in Show Magazine., 3/65 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Jackson Hole (WB), 1965
  - Casting selection list with PNA., ND; 6 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Cast selection list with PNA., 4/19/65; 2 pgs.
  - Cast Selection list with PNA., ND; 4 pgs.
  - Interview schedule and notes with OPNA., ND; 7 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Farmer parts. P., ND
  - Drawings and maps of Jackson Hole., NDawings; 6 oversize (smaller than folio) sheets. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Locations research and drawings with notes. maps., ND; 7 pgs.
  - Area map and diagram and sketches. P., ND; 12 pgs, 5 pgs on both sides. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Narration part., ND (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Exterior and interior setting with PNAD and T notes., ND; 5 pgs.
  - Breakdown of scenes., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Tentative pre- and post-production shooting schedule., ND (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Tentative working days out of days for cast and crew on location., 6/4/65; Legal. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Diamond D Productions: series of Westerns by DD--promotional ad for Jackson Hole., ND; 3 copies T. 3 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - TLS H. H. Swanson (agency) to DD re: reissue of original book., 5/25/65 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Characterizations. M., ND; 11 copies. [UNK] pgs. each. (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Incomplete final script-SP by DD from novel by Giles A. Lutz- The Honyockers., 6/1/65; 145 pgs. (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Estimating Draft, 5/11/65; (2 copies). M. 146 pgs. each. (Box 75, Folder 21, 22)
  - SP by DD., 3/29/65; 3 copies, 1 T original and 2 M copies. 146 pgs. each. (Box 76, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - Production cross-plot - actors and scenes. P., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - BW photos of artists. 39 8" × 10" photo composites with 12 pictures on each, each picture 2" × 2"., ND (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Invitation to Pink Garter Theater in Jackson Hole. Printed., ND; 4 " × 5". (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Index to Breakdown. Jackson Hole, 6/1/65; 117 pgs. (Box 76, Folder 7)
- The Wilding (unfinished)
  - Exploratory draft and notes., ND; ca. 150 pgs. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Breakdown and mockup of novel, with notes. in 3 ring binder, ND (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Original novel, ElsieVenner by Oliver Wendell Holmes cut and pasted on paper with FPpNAD and revisions by DD., ND; ca. 300 pgs. both sides. (Box 77, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4)
  - Delmer Daves: Dokumentation von Joachim Kveck Book re: Daves, in Gevman, April, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 5)
EXPLANATION
The inventory to the Delmar Daves' cartoon collection is arranged exactly as the Files came to Stanford University. Mr. Daves had a broad subject arrangement subdivided by further subject classification within the broad areas. The classification does not follow an alphabetical arrangement and in some instances there is a repetition of subjects. However, no attempt to reorganize the collection has been made.
The inventory is an exact duplication of the subject files and serves as a very general index. Under each subdivision the individual cartoons, often three or four to a page, are mounted on large legal sheets. The collection is contained in six legal file drawers.
Inventory to the Delmar Daves' Cartoon Collection
- ART
  - Sculpture
  - Artists and Models
  - Artists at Work
  - Art Dealers
  - Art Galleries
  - Art Students
  - Museums
- AVIATION
  - Astronauts - Space Travel, Etc.
  - Balloons
  - Private Planes
  - Air Travel
  - Airport
- ANIMALS
  - Dinosaurs - Museums
  - Pet Shops
  - Aquarium
  - Hospitals - Nurses, Internes
  - Surgery
  - Chiropodist
  - Chiropractor, Osteopath
  - Funerals, Epitaphs
  - Hangovers
  - Death-beds, Wills, and Legacies
  - Occulists, Optometrists
  - Accidents, Ambulences
  - Sick Room - Ailments
  - First Aid
- BODY AILING
  - Doctor's Office Waiting Room
  - Doctors
  - Medical Research
  - Diagnoses
  - Dentists
  - Psychologists, Psychiatrists
  - Maternity Ward
- CARICATURE AND CARTOONS
  - Strictly American
  - Interesting Human Anecdotes
- CHILDREN
  - Boys Swimming and Fishing
  - Boys Playing Soldier
  - Boys Fighting
  - Boys Playing Baseball and Football
  - Children at Camp, Beach, Etc.
  - Children's Picnics, Circus Fairs, Theater
  - Baby Sitters
  - Children's Imagination
  - Adolescents
  - Girl and Boy Scouts and Brownies
  - Children Shopping
  - Little Lulu
  - Children - Miscellaneous Situations
  - Children around the House
  - Children - Miscellaneous Situations (Pocket 2)
  - Child Prodigies - Movie Children, Etc.
  - Children at Church - Sunday School
  - Children Romance
  - Children's Parties - Dancing School
  - Children and Christmas
  - Babies
  - Children Playing Indoors
  - Children Playing Outdoors
  - Children on the Farm
  - Getting them to eat and take medicine.
  - Children - Music Lessons, Public Appearances, Recitals
  - Bedtime, Story-telling, Etc.
- EXPLORATION
  - Explorers - Mountaineering
  - Explorers - Arctic
  - Explorers - Jungles
  - Isolation
  - Anywhere in the U.S.A. except the South
  - The South
  - Europe
  - Foreign Scents
  - Indians
  - Mexico
  - Historic Americana
  - Archaelogists and Other Scientists in the Field and Museum
- TRANSPORTATION - SHIP WRECKS
  - At Sea and Adrift
  - On an Island
- TRANSPORTATION - STEAMSHIPS
  - At Sea - Officers, Crew
  - Travel Bureau - Information
  - At Sea - Life on the Deck, Staterooms
  - Excursions and Aboard Ship - Abroad
  - Private Yachts
  - In Harbor
  - Boat and Yacht Shows
  - Lighthouses, Etc.
  - Launching - Steamships, Battleships
  - Fishing Boats, Tugboats, Ferries, Houseboats, Etc.
  - Customs
  - Tourists
- INCOME TAX
  - Income Tax
- INVENTORS AND SCIENTISTS
  - Inventors & Scientists No. 1
  - Inventors & Scientists No. 2
  - Scientists - Space
- THE LAW
  - Courtroom & Trials 1. Judges 2. Lawyers 3. Jury
  - Criminals. Captured - Patrol Wagon
  - Criminals - Third Degree
  - Criminals - Women
- MARRIED LIFE
  - Across the Table
  - Friendly Exchanges Between Mr. adn Mrs.
  - Friendly Exchanges No. 2
  - Screwball Doings
  - Thurber Subtleties
  - Beautiful but Dumb Wives
  - Henpecked Husband
  - Company - Neighbors
  - Conflicts
  - Triangles - Jealousies
  - Before and after
  - Going Home to Mother
  - Rendezvous with Hubby
  - Newlyweds
- PARTIES
  - Parties, Dinner
  - Complaints of Neighbors
  - Birthday Parties
  - Parties - Luncheons, Bridge
  - Dances - Dancing
  - Teas - Bazaars
  - Costume
  - Cocktail
  - Formal
  - Informal
- FIGHTS
  - Brawls- Drunks - Duels - Riots - Man to Man
- SPORTS
  - Swimming
  - Crew
  - Riding
  - Track
  - Bowling
  - Wrestling
  - Water Sports
  - Boxing
  - Polo
  - Tennis - Badminton, Ping-Pong
  - Mountain Climbing
  - Golf
  - Indoor Sports - Bridge, Poker, Chess, Checkers, Gambling, Billiards, Pool, etc.
  - Auto Racing - Bicycle Races
  - Horse Racing
  - Dog Racing
  - Basketball
  - Baseball
- ENTERTAINMENT WORLD - THEATRE
  - Ballet
  - Opera
  - Theatre - Amateur - Barn Theatres
  - Vaudeville (see: Hight Clubs)
  - Burlesque
  - Legitimate
- ENTERTAINMENT WORLD - RADIO & TELEVISION
  - Radio & TV: 1. At Broadcasting and TV Stations
  - Radio & TV: 2. On location
  - Radio & TV: 3. Audience
  - TV and Radio on Sets
  - Radio & Television Stores & Repairs
- ENTERTAINMENT WORLD - MOVIES
  - Theatre and Audiences
  - Actors, Actresses, Publicity Agents, Booking Agents
  - Studio - On Sets
  - Studio - Executives
  - On Location
  - Studio - Writers
- CIRCUS - FAIRS
  - Circus
  - Bazaars
  - Parades
  - Rodeos
  - Fairs - Carnivals & Entertainment Parks
  - The Perfect Squelch
  - Tales of Hoffman -- Index--Reader's Digest
  - Keeping Up With the World -- Bits of Knowledge
  - Personalities & Behavior -- Types Men & Women
  - United Nations -- Security Council
  - Character -- Bad --Arrogant people, etc.
  - Character -- Good - Benefactors, etc.
  - Items of the Reader's Digest Type
  - Famous Last Words
  - Tall Tales
  - Compendiums of various types of experiences by various people
  - Snappy Comebacks -- Retorts Courteous
  - Picturesque Speech & Patter
  - Witticisms - Philosophies
  - Bearing on the Communist Angle - Red-baiting, etc.
- STORES
  - Hardware, etc. (see also Business: Furn. Stores)
  - Furniture Stores
  - Pawnbrokers - Antiques - Auctions
  - Lower Class Merchants
  - Shoe Stores
  - Shoe Repair - Cleaning and PRESSING
  - Bootblacks
  - Department Store -- Information
  - Department Stores -- Elevators - Escalators
  - Complaint Dept. - Lost and Found
  - Milliners and Dressmakers
  - Drug Store
- BUSINESS
  - Stenographers
  - Armored Cars
  - Banks - Loan Offices
  - Corporations - Advertising & Publicity
  - Waiting Rooms - Receptionists
  - Factories
  - Agents, Sales Organizations, etc.
  - Corporations - Office Workers
  - Corporations - Executives
  - Directors' Meetings - Stockholders Meeting
- TRADESMEN
  - Milkman - Breadman
  - Grocer
  - Butcher
  - Miscellaneous
- EMPLOYMENT
  - Employment Agency
  - Applying for Job
  - Depression - Hard Times - Bread Lines - Relief
  - Picketing - Strikes - Union Meetings - Labor Boards
  - Help Wanted
  - Sandwich Men
  - Out of Work
- WAR - ARMY
  - Camp: K.P. Duty - Cooks - Mess
  - Army: Peace Time - Northwest Mounted, etc.
  - Marines
  - M.P.s
  - Guided Missiles
  - Army: Signal Corps - Carrier Pigeons, etc. - Camouflage
  - Army: On Leave - Requests for Leave
  - Camp: Visitors
  - Army: In Camp
  - War: Returning Home Heroes
  - Camp: Inspection
  - Mail From Home - Mail Censors
  - U.S.O. Parties, Dances, Entertainment
  - Camp: Sentries
  - Guard House
  - Yanks Abroad
  - P.O.W.
  - Army: Training - Maneuvers
  - Inductees - Raw Recruits - Recruiting - Drafting - Draft Board Exam
  - Sargeants
  - Army: Hospitals, Nurses, Ambulances, etc.
  - Army: Troop Trains - Troop ships -- Leave Taking -- R.R. Stations
  - Army - Officers -- Navy - Officers
  - Army: Tank Corps
  - Spies: Military Secrets
  - Army - In Action
- WAR - FOREIGN
  - Foreign
  - Britain at War
  - Foreign Legion
- WAR - AIR CORPS (see: AVIATION)
  - Army: Anti-Aircraft
  - Air Corps - In Action
  - Pilots
  - Aviation Schools - Pilot Training
  - War - Washington - Desk Generals
  - Ground Crew
  - Parachutes - Paratroops
- WAR - NAVY
  - Navy: On Board Ship
  - Submarines
  - On Leave - Requesting Leave
  - Battleship Launching
  - Training
- WAR: HOME FRONT ACTIVITIES
  - Women in Uniform
  - Miscellaneous - Civil War - quotations, etc.
  - Folks Back Home
  - Home Defense - Blackouts - Air Wardens, etc.
  - Defense Workers - Men -- Defense Projects
  - Rationing
  - War Activities on Home Front: Red Cross - Blood Banks - Bundles for War Victims, etc.
  - Women in War Plants
  - Locations - Hawaii, Philippines, Alaska
- ROMANCE
  - Honeymooning
  - Elopement
  - Proposals - (a) Asking for Daughter's Hand
  - Flirtation - Boy Meets Girl
  - Engagements - Marriage License Bureaus
  - Ship Romances
  - Lady Killers
  - Jealousy
  - Love Making in Public Places
  - Love Making - A. Around the House
  - B. In the Car
  - C. In the Park
  - D. On the Water
  - E. Outdoors
  - On the Make
  - Parents of Lovers - Little Brothers and Sisters
  - Weddings
  - Dates
- GIRLS
  - Bobby Soxers
  - Cats and Gossips
  - Dizzy Dames
  - Golddiggers
  - Theatre - Musical Comedies a. Chorus Girls
  - Twins - Normal Girls
- MEN (Types)
  - Old Boys at the Club
  - Gamblers
  - Lazy Men
  - Rich Men
  - Irishmen, Scotchmen, Jews - Dislect Jokes
  - Heroes
  - Beatnicks
  - Raconteurs
  - After Dinner Speakers
  - Kentucky Colonel
  - Fat Men
  - Milquetoasts (See also Married Life - Henpecked Husbands)
  - Egotists - Eccentrics
  - Foreigners
  - Hot Tempers
  - Pansies - Saps
  - Playboys
  - Bachelor - Young Men
  - Bores - Snobs
  - Average Men
  - Drunks
  - Bums, Hoboes, Panhandlers - (see Freight Trains)
  - Old Roues
  - Miscellaneous